hscripts.com 2014-09-21

# FREE SCRIPTs, PHP, Perl Tutorials, gif clipart Images, JavaScript, JSP, Ajax, Regex, Adobe Photoshop Tutorial, Linux Commands, Web master Tool : Hscripts.com Privacy Policy

We at Hscripts.com are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites.

The following Online Privacy Policy for the Hscripts.com website so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of Hscripts.com regarding information we collect on our website, including but not limited to email, newsletters, and leave-behinds. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Hscripts.com does not have control, or to people that Hscripts.com does not employ.

Information Collected by Hscripts.com 

####  Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information 

Hscripts.com collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the Hscripts.com site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. 

Hscripts.com may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

####  Personally Identifiable Consumer Information 

In addition, at some of the Hscripts.com web sites, we collect information (i) that you may choose to provide to us when requesting additional information from us or from one or more of our clients, (ii) when you register or sign up on one of our web sites, including our forums, and (iii) that you provide when accessing products and services that require registration such as white papers, newsletters and other communications with one of our web sites. Examples of personally identifiable data that you may provide to us include name, phone number, address, and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below. 

####  How Collected Information is Used 

The non-personally identifiable information that Hscripts.com collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If you elect to provide Hscripts.com with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Hscripts.com and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other Hscripts.com sales and marketing efforts. The resume information you may elect to provide is used as part of our job board services and will be made available to third parties if you so elect as described elsewhere in this policy. 

####  Sharing Information with Third Parties 

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by Hscripts.com. There are instances, however, in which you’re personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of Hscripts.com on an anonymous basis. Hscripts.com may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials. 

####  Security 

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within Hscripts.com or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while Hscripts.com will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

####  Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out 

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your web site activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting Hscripts.com web site. 

####  Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out 

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to Hscripts.com. If you choose to provide such information to Hscripts.com, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you have subscribed to receive multiple newsletters and/or announcement lists, you can either unsubscribe from each one separately by following the instructions at the bottom of the emails that you receive. In addition, if you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out by sending an e-mail to us at privacy@hscripts.com and providing your email address and a list of communications that you want to unsubscribe from. 

####  Access/Accuracy 

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, Hscripts.com wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Hscripts.com should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to privacy@hscripts.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable. 

####  Children's Privacy 

Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

####  Commitment 

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Hscripts.com’s web site is constantly changing to meet these demands. 

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@hscripts.com . While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Hscripts.com 's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

####  Contacting us 

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding Hscripts.com’s Privacy Policy, you may email us at [ privacy@hscripts.com ](mailto:support@hscripts.com).
